topdesignfirms.com 2004-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Information Collection and Use**

TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Email Forms**

Your information will be collected on various email forms on our site. These forms are used for the sole purpose of sending the collected information to TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM. Unless otherwise noted on the specific page containing the form, TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM is sole recipient of that information.

**Directory Inclusion**

Should you choose to be included in our directory you may infrequently receive announcements from us pertaining to our website and services. These announcements may include, but are not limited to, special offers, website updates, changes to this privacy policy, etc. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, we can limit your voting in our poll to only one vote, or control our banner ads so you don't see the same one too many times. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site without any drawbacks.

**Log Files**

In log files we collect your IP address, referring site URL, time, and date.

We use IP addresses, etc. to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We partner with online quoting vendors to provide specific services. When you use our quoting service, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information, such as e-mail and postal address or phone number, except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys and Polls**

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or polls. Participation in these surveys or polls is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address) and comments regarding your thoughts about our site. This information is sometimes immediately displayed on our site for others to view. Do not provide any information that you do not want others to view. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our site.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask you for the friend's name and e-mail address. TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting him/her to visit the site. TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact TOPDESIGNFIRMS.COM at our contact page to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desks. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, please send an e-mail through our contact page.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to a court order or comply with a legal process served on our Web site. We will provide prior notification of such request(s) either by e-mail or written notice.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. You can choose not to have your information used.
